I
insurance we protect our cars our homes
the things we value simple but what
about life insurance seems complicated
right it doesn't have to be simply put
life insurance is about providing
financial protection for the people you
care about whether you're making sure
your beneficiaries can manage debt or
the costs of living or if you want to
leave them with a lasting financial
legacy the right life insurance coverage
can help provide options for those you
care about most by giving them choices
there are two types of life insurance
term and permanent term insurance is
temporary you buy it for a set period of
time 10 or 20 years to ensure your
beneficiaries aren't burdened with
financial obligations like ongoing
living expenses or a mortgage term
insurance is often very affordable but
remember once the term ends so does your
protection permanent insurance like
whole life or universal life is well
permanent it stays with you for life
allowing you to leave a financial legacy
for the people you care about while it
can be more expensive than term
insurance permanent insurance features
investment opportunities that can allow
the value of your policy to grow over
time potentially increasing the worth of
your estate term permanent both your
advisor can help you go beyond the basic
center